https://www.ucr.edu/privacy.html

Breadcrumb
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Policy
The University of California, Riverside is committed to ensuring the privacy and accuracy of your confidential information to the extent possible, subject to provisions of state and federal law. Other than as required by laws that guarantee public access to certain types of information, or in response to subpoenas or other legal instruments that authorize access, personally-identifiable information is not actively shared. In particular, we do not re-distribute or sell personal information collected on our web servers.
Information Collected
UCR websites may collect personal information such as name, address, e-mail address, telephone number(s), and/or educational interests. Such personal information may be requested by us for research, public service or teaching programs, or for administrative purposes. Additional personal information, such as credit card account information, may be requested for purchases or enrollment purposes.
Web servers typically collect, at least temporarily, the following information: Internet Protocol (IP) address of computer being used; web pages requested; referring web page; browser used; date and time. UCR may collect statistics identifying particular IP addresses from which our websites are accessed.
Use of Collected Information
UCR may use personal information collected from websites for the purpose of future communication back to online enrollees, in order to keep you informed of such activities as campus programs, symposia and/or special events, but only if you are provided the opportunity to opt out of that type of use.
UCR may use browser-IP-address information and anonymous-browser history to report information about site accesses and for statistical purposes. This information is generally used to improve Web presentation and utilization. The campus also may use IP address information for troubleshooting purposes.
Some UCR online activity sites may use "cookies" in order to deliver web content specific to individual users' interests or to keep track of online purchasing transactions. Sensitive personal information is not stored within cookies.
Distribution of Collected Information
UCR will not disclose, without your consent, personal information collected about you, except for certain explicit circumstances in which disclosure is required by law.
UCR will not distribute or sell personal information to third-party organizations.
Individual Choice
Individuals who wish to use methods other than online enrollment may submit requests by e-mail or U.S. mail addressed to the UC Riverside organization responsible for the website.
Access to Your Own Information
Questions regarding users' rights to review, modify or delete their previously provided personal information should be directed to the campus organization to which they provided the information. Any disputes will be resolved under existing records regulations applicable to UCR.
Main Campus Site
The main campus site (i.e. www.ucr.edu) in addition to general logs, also collects usage information the links on its pages. This information is only used in an aggregate form to determine how resources are used.
×
Let us help you with your search
Enter your Search Criteria.
Search
Cancel
